All right.
We're going to reenter our regular we're leaving Executive Session, going back to our regular scheduled meeting at 09:32
p. M.
Do we have any open items that need to be cleared up?
>> I would make a motion that we
approve the tax adjustments
as noted in the packet.
>> I will second.
All right. Further discussion on that?
Okay.
All those in favor?
All those opposed?
Okay.
We moving on?
>> So that one is four to one. So can I have a request? Because the ones since August are still sitting in the thing waiting to be signed.
>> So you could probably come in and sign like a whole I'll come sign them because the board chose to vote against me.
>> Okay. I don't know if you can sign them considering you voted against.
>> It seems It seems You know what? Adrian, if you'd like to sign them, you're more than welcome to. I think Paula's going down there for a meeting tomorrow. She can do it. Okay. Eric, Eric, I'll be in to sign them.
Right. It's further Mereliction of duty.
Okay. Who wants to make the motion to adjourn? Motion to adjourn.
Second. Second. All those in favor? Aye. Aye. Thank you very much. We'll see you guys later. Have good night, guys. Peace. Bye. Good night. Have fun in the morning.